Guide to the Stan Healy Photographs and Papers 1890s-1990s (bulk 1940s-1970s)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Accession 1990-016 Photographs, circa 1890s-1970s; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (2,700 images)
  - Dedication of Interstate 90 at Bonner, 1964; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1190)
  - Dedication of Interstate 90 at Bonner, 1964; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1191)
  - Dedication of Interstate 90 at Bonner, 1964; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1192)
  - Dedication of Interstate 90 at Bonner, 1964; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1193)
  - Congressman Arnold Olsen inspecting Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1194)
  - Congressman Arnold Olsen inspecting Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1195)
  - Congressman Arnold Olsen inspecting Interstate 90, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1196)
  - Congressman Arnold Olsen inspecting Interstate 90, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1197)
  - Congressman Arnold Olsen inspecting Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1198)
  - Congressman Arnold Olsen inspecting Interstate 90 with group, 1966 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1199)
  - Congressman Arnold Olsen inspecting Interstate 90 with group, 1966 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1200)
  - Congressman Arnold Olsen talking with people at Reserve Street interchange (2 photos), 1966; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1201)
  - Van Buren Interchange on Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1202)
  - Construction of Interstate 90, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-1203)
  - Construction of Interstate 90, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-1204)
  - Van Buren Interchange on Interstate 90, undated; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1205)
  - Van Buren Interchange on Interstate 90, undated; (2 photos) (Box 3, Photo number 90-1206)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 at Milltown/Bonner, 1964 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1207)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 at Milltown/Bonner, 1964 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1208)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 at Milltown/Bonner, 1964 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1209)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 at Milltown/Bonner, 1964 (Box 3, Photo number 90-1210)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 at Milltown/Bonner, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1211)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 at Milltown/Bonner, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1212)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 at Milltown/Bonner, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1213)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1214)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1215)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1216)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1217)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1218)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1219)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1220)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1221)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1222)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1223)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1224)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1225)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1226)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 overpass between Clinton and Milltown, 1963; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1227)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 near Orange Street, Missoula, Montana, July 19, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1228A)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 near Orange Street looking southeast from Waterworks Hill, Missoula, Montana, July 19, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1228B)
  - Interstate 90 being paved near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1229)
  - Equipment paving Interestate 90 near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1230)
  - Equipment paving Interestate 90 near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1231)
  - Equipment paving Interestate 90 near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1232)
  - Equipment paving Interestate 90 near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1233)
  - Equipment paving Interestate 90 near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1234)
  - Equipment paving Interestate 90 near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1235)
  - Construction of Orange Street Interchange, Interstate 90, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1236)
  - Construction of Orange Street Interchange, Interstate 90, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1237)
  - View of paving Interstate 90 from building, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1238)
  - View of paving Interstate 90 from building, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1239)
  - Construction of Orange Street Interchange, Interstate 90, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1240)
  - Interstate 90 being paved near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1241)
  - Equipment paving Interestate 90 near Missoula, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1242)
  - Surveyor stakes for sidewalk construction on Orange Street, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1243)
  - Construction of curb at Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1244)
  - Construction of curb at Orange Street interchange, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1245)
  - Interstate 90 being paved near Missoula, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1246)
  - Interstate 90 being paved near Missoula, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1247)
  - Construction of curb at Orange Street interchange, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1248)
  - Construction of curb at Orange Street interchange, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1249)
  - Construction of curb at Orange Street interchange, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1250)
  - Interstate 90 being paved near Missoula, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1251)
  - Interstate 90 being paved near Missoula, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1252)
  - Interstate 90 being paved near Missoula, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1253)
  - Construction work on Orange Street interchange with Healy house in background, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1254)
  - Construction work on Orange Street interchange with Healy house in background, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1255)
  - Construction work on Orange Street interchange with Healy house in background, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1256)
  - Construction of Orange Street Interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1257)
  - Construction of Orance Street Interchange, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1258)
  - Construction work on Orange Street interchange with Healy house in background, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1259)
  - Paving and installing dividers on Interstate 90, 1966; (4 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1260)
  - Paving of Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1261)
  - Paving and installing dividers on Interstate 90; aerial shot and car on road, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1262)
  - Paving and installing dividers on Interstate 90; aerial shot and close-up, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1263)
  - Paving and installing dividers on Interstate 90; aerial shot and close-up, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1264)
  - Paving and installing dividers on Interstate 90; aerial shots, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1265)
  - Construction of Interstate 90, 1966; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1266)
  - Stan Healy residence off Interstate 90 Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1267)
  - Stan Healy residence off Interstate 90 Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1268)
  - Stan Healy residence off Interstate 90 Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1269)
  - Stan Healy residence off Interstate 90 Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1270)
  - Stan Healy residence off Interstate 90 Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1271)
  - Stan Healy residence off Interstate 90 Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1272)
  - Stan Healy residence off Interstate 90 Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1273)
  - Stan Healy residence off Interstate 90 Orange Street interchange, 1966 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1274)
  - Interstate 90 bridge between Alberton and Superior, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1275)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 bridge between Alberton and Superior, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1276)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 bridge between Alberton and Superior over Clark Fork River, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1277)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 bridge between Alberton and Superior over Clark Fork River, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1278)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 bridge between Alberton and Superior over Clark Fork River, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1279)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 bridge between Alberton and Superior over Clark Fork River, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1280)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 bridge between Alberton and Superior over Clark Fork River, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1281)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 bridge between Alberton and Superior over Clark Fork River, 1964 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1282)
  - Preparing for Interstate 90 dedication, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1283)
  - Ribbon cutting at Interstate 90 dediction, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1284)
  - Dedication ceremony for Interstate 90, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1285)
  - Dedication ceremony for Interstate 90 with horses, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1286)
  - Dedication ceremony for Interstate 90, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1287)
  - Ribbon cutting at Interstate 90 dediction, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1288)
  - Ribbon cutting at Interstate 90 dediction, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1289)
  - Dedication ceremony for Interstate 90 with horses, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1290)
  - Ribbon cutting at Interstate 90 dediction, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1291)
  - Ribbon cutting at Interstate 90 dediction, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1292)
  - Ribbon cutting at Interstate 90 dediction, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1293)
  - Dedication ceremony for Interstate 90, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1294)
  - Cars driving on Interstate 90, 1965; (3 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1295)
  - Dedication ceremony for Interstate 90, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1296)
  - Dedication ceremony for Interstate 90, cars on interstate, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1297)
  - Broken sidewalk on 3rd street before repaving, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1298)
  - Teepees on an island in the Clark Fork River, near downtown Missoula, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1299)
  - View of Missoula, Mt. Sentinel with Clark Fork River in foreground, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1300)
  - View of Clark Fork River, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1301)
  - View of Missoula, Mt. Sentinel with Clark Fork River in foreground, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1302)
  - Clark Fork River, 1955 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1303)
  - Clark Fork River, 1955 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1304)
  - Clark Fork River in Missoula, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1305)
  - Clark Fork River in Missoula, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1306)
  - Construction of Russell Street bridge, Missoula, 1956 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1307)
  - Construction of Russell Street bridge, Missoula, 1956 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1308)
  - Construction of Russell Street bridge over Clark Fork River, Missoula, 1956 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1309)
  - Construction of Russell Street bridge, Missoula, 1956; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1310)
  - Construction of Russell Street bridge over Clark Fork River, Missoula, 1956; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1311)
  - Construction of Russell Street bridge, Missoula, 1956; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1312)
  - Construction of Russell Street bridge, Missoula, 1956; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1313)
  - Construction of New Higgins Ave. bridge, near Montagne building, 1962 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1314)
  - Construction of New Higgins Ave. bridge, 1962 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1315)
  - Construction of New Higgins Ave. bridge, 1962 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1316)
  - Construction of New Higgins Ave. bridge, 1962 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1317)
  - Construction on New Higgins Ave. bridge over Clark Fork, 1962 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1318)
  - New Higgins Ave. bridge looking North, 1962 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1319)
  - Site of future Russell Street Bridge, view of road, undated; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1320)
  - Site of future Russell Street Bridge, view of road, undated; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1321)
  - Site of future Russell Street Bridge, view of Clark Fork River, undated; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1322)
  - Bonner dam, close up, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1323)
  - Bonner dam, wide shot, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1324)
  - Lincoln/Russell St. bridge under construction, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1325)
  - Lincoln/Russell St. bridge under construction, 1957; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1326)
  - Lincoln/Russell St. bridge under construction, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1327)
  - Lincoln/Russell St. bridge under construction, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1328)
  - Closing Russell Street during bridge construction, 1957; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1329)
  - Closing Russell Street during bridge construction, 1957; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1330)
  - Closing Russell Street during bridge construction, street view, 1957; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1331)
  - Closing Russell Street during bridge construction, 1957; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1332)
  - Russell Street bridge under construction, crane in the Clark Fork river bed, Missoula, Montana, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1333A)
  - Russell Street bridge under construction, looking north on Russell Street and Don's Food Market, Missoula, Montana, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1333B)
  - Clark Fork River during Russell Street bridge construction, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1334)
  - Clark Fork River during Russell Street bridge construction, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1335)
  - Clark Fork River during Russell Street bridge construction, street view, 1957; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1336)
  - Russell Street bridge under construction, 1956 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1337)
  - Lincoln/Russell Street bridge under construction, 1956 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1338)
  - Clark Fork River during Lincold/Russell Street bridge construction, 1956 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1339)
  - Lincoln/Russell Street bridge under construction, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1340)
  - Clark Fork River during Lincold/Russell Street bridge construction, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1341)
  - Clark Fork River during Lincold/Russell Street bridge construction, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1342)
  - Lincoln/Russell Street bridge under construction, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1343)
  - Lincoln/Russell Street bridge under construction, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1344)
  - Lincoln/Russell Street bridge under construction, undated; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1345)
  - Orange Street bridge ditch being widened, undated; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1346)
  - Orange Street bridge ditch being widened, undated; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1347)
  - Unknown bridge from dirt road, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1348)
  - Unknown bridge from dirt road, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1349)
  - View of river from under unknown bridge, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1350)
  - Aerial view of river and unknown bridge, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1351)
  - Aerial view of river and unknown bridge, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1352)
  - Unknown bridge in snow, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1353)
  - Views of Orange Street bridge, Aerial and from riverbank, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1354)
  - Bridge over Clark Fork River, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1355)
  - Higgins Ave. bridge from riverbank, looking at river from bridge, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1356)
  - Unknown bridge, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1357)
  - Unknown bridge, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1358)
  - Railroad bridge over Clark Fork River, 1956 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1359)
  - Unknown bridge, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1360)
  - Men working on unknown bridge, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1361)
  - Madison Street bridge in snow, 1959; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1362)
  - View of street in snow, children posing in front of large snow pile, 1959; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1363)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge from banks of the Clark Fork River, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1364)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge from banks of the Clark Fork River, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1365)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge from banks of the Clark Fork River, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1366)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge from banks of the Clark Fork River, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1367)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge, close up, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1368)
  - Equipment used in construction of Madison Street Bridge, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1369)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1370)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1371)
  - View of Higgins Ave. bridge from banks of Clark Fork River, towards downtown, 1951 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1372)
  - View of Higgins Ave. bridge from banks of Clark Fork River, towards downtown, 1951 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1373)
  - View of Higgins Ave. bridge from banks of Clark Fork River, 1951 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1374)
  - Wilma Theatre, Higgins Ave. bridge while decking is torn off, 1951 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1375)
  - Street view of Higgins Ave. bridge while decking is torn off, 1951 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1376)
  - Higgins Ave. bridge from riverbank, looking north, 1951 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1377)
  - Wilma Theatre, Higgins Ave. bridge while decking is torn off, street view, 1951 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1378)
  - Buckhouse bridge prior to collapse, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1379)
  - Buckhouse bridge prior to collapse, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1380)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge, 1957 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1381)
  - Construction of Madison Street Bridge from banks of the Clark Fork River, over railroad tracks, 1957; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1382)
  - Collapse of footbridge with equipment, 1953 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1383)
  - Collapse of footbridge with equipment, railroad tracks in foreground, 1953 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1384)
  - Collapse of footbridge with equipment, 1953 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1385)
  - Buckhouse bridge after collapse, from banks of river, 1955 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1386)
  - Crew redecking the Higgins Ave. Bridge, towards downtown, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1387)
  - Higgins Ave. bridge from bank of Clark Fork river, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1388)
  - Crew working on railroad bridge with Higgins Ave. bridge in foreground, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1389)
  - Collapse of unknown bridge during flood, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1390)
  - Bonner dam during the flood on 1908 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1391)
  - Higgins Ave bridge collapse during flood of 1908 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1392)
  - Higgins Ave bridge collapse during flood of 1908, from banks of Clark Fork (Box 4, Photo number 90-1393)
  - Picture of 1908 flood as viewed from Beavertail Hill (Box 4, Photo number 90-1394)
  - House ravaged by 1908 flood near Missoula (Box 4, Photo number 90-1395)
  - Picture of work on Higgins St. bridge during the flood of 1908 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1396)
  - House ravaged by 1908 flood near Missoula, along Rattlesnake Creek (Box 4, Photo number 90-1397)
  - Picture of Higgins St. bridge during 1908 flood (Box 4, Photo number 90-1398)
  - Homes during the 1908 flood (Box 4, Photo number 90-1399)
  - Rattlesnake Creek, Greenough Park during 1908 flood; mansion off to the side (Box 4, Photo number 90-1400)
  - Steamboat on Flathead Lake, unknown man in forground standing on dock, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1401)
  - Steamboat on Flathead Lake, unknown woman in forground standing on dock, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1402)
  - Map of federal land sale around Flathead Lake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1403)
  - Picture of views of old levels on Flathead Lake, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1404)
  - Children on bunny float during a parade over the Higgins St. bridge, facing North, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1405)
  - Marching bank during parade over the Higgins St. bridge, facing North, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1406)
  - Float being pulled by car during parade over Higgins Ave. bridge, facing north, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1407)
  - Butterfly float pulled by car during parade over Higgins Ave. bridge, facing north, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1408)
  - Police followed by marching band during parade over Higgins Ave. bridge, facing north, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1409)
  - Construction on Interstate 90 over river, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1410)
  - Construction on Interstate 90 over river, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1411)
  - Construction on Interstate 90 over river, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1412)
  - Construction on Interstate 90 over river, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1413)
  - Construction on Interstate 90 over river, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1414)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 at Cyr, railroad tracks in foreground, undated (Box 4, Photo number 90-1415)
  - Construction of Orange Street interchange, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1416)
  - Construction of Orange Street interchange, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1417)
  - View of Orange Street interchange from hill, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1418)
  - View of Orange Street interchange from hill, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1419)
  - Construction of Interstate 90 from neighborhood near Missoula, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1420)
  - View of Orange Street interchange from hill, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1421)
  - Close up of bridge during construction of Orange Street interchange, dirt road, 1965; (2 photos) (Box 4, Photo number 90-1422)
  - Construction of Orange Street interchange from neighborhood, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1423)
  - Construction of Orange Street interchange from neighborhood, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1424)
  - Construction of Orange Street interchange from neighborhood, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1425)
  - View of Orange Street interchange from hill, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1426)
  - Healy home looking north, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1427)
  - Construction of Orange Street interchange from neighborhood, 1965 (Box 4, Photo number 90-1428)